ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5619/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Target, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  October, November 1987
- Target, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  July - September 1987
- Target, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  May-June 1987
- Target Correspondence, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  May and June 1988
- Target Correspondence, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  April 1988
- Target Correspondence, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  March 1988
- Target Correspondence, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  February 1988
- Target Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  November 1988 to March 1989
- Target, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  January 1989
- Unnamed Files, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Unnamed Files, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Staff Meetings, Etc., 1988 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Fletcherville, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- MacClenny Products, Inc, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Tahari, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Negotiating Kent Committee, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Target CBA, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Negotiations ACTWU Proposals, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Kent I and II, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Negotiations Correspondence, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Kent II, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Jaguar Appealed Grievances, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Jaguar Manufacturing Company Negotiations, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Jaguar Manufacturing Company: CBA, 1969-1982 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Jaguar Mismanagement, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Jackson, Lewis, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Time Studies/Engineering, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 18)
- P.W. Lining, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  #35 PW K.-II
- MacClenny Products, Incorporated, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Target Strike Settlement Agreement, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  November 14, 1988
- Negotiations Co. Proposals, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- Dillon Manufacturing, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 23)
- National Labor Board Relations Subpoenas, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Target ULP's, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 25)
- Info Requests, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 26)
- Surveys, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 27)
- Dillon Manufacturing, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 28)
- Target (Clearfield) Health Care Survey, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Target Tales Company Newsletter, 1983-1987 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Dillon Manufacturing Incorporated, 1986-1988 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Target [1 of 5], 1990 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Target [2 of 5], 1988 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  July-December 1989
- Target [3 of 5], 1989 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  April-May 1989
- Target [4 of 5], 1989 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  August-December 1989
- Target [5 of 5], 1989 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  June/July 1989
- Target Sportswear Incorporated CBA, 1966-1988 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Target Newsletter, 1986-1987 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Target Newsletters, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Target Exhibit "D" Sample Sales Materials, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Darryl R. Martin Beck Letter, 1988-1989 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Brookvale Manufacturing, 1985-1988 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- KGW Correspondence, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Current Issues from H Raynor, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Bob Lenhard, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Bob Lenhard Expenses, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- H.R. Steward Training Class, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- Unnamed Files, 1984-1987 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Kent Sportswear Incorporated CBA, 1956-1985 (Box 61, Folder 21)
- Joint Boards: General, 1980-1987 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Services and Allied Industries Joint Board, 1984-1987 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board, 1985-1987 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Bi-County and Northern North Carolina Joint Board (Textile), 1983-1987 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Buffalo Joint Board, 1985-1987 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- California Joint Board, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- California Joint Board (Rothstein File), 1984-1987 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Canadian Office: Clothing Division, 1983-1987 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- General Canadian Joint Boards, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Catawba Valley Joint Board, 1983-1987 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Central Alabama Georgia Joint Board, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Central North Carolina Joint Board, 1982-1986 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Central and South Jersey Joint Board, 1983-1987 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Chicago Joint Board, 1982-1987 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Chicago and Central States (Chicago) Joint Board, 1981-1987 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Chicago and Central States (Chicago) Joint Board, 1981-1987 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Cincinnati Joint Board, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Cleveland Joint Board, 1985-1987 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- Colorado Regional Joint Board, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- Deep South Regional, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 20)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Clothing Workers Joint Board, 1986-1987 (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Eastern Shore Joint Board, 1984-1985 (Box 62, Folder 22)
- El Paso Joint Board, 1984-1987 (Box 62, Folder 23)
- Georgia Joint Board, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 24)
- Georgia Tennessee Alabama Joint Board, 1985-1986 (Box 62, Folder 25)
- Greater Cornwall Joint Board, 1984-1987 (Box 62, Folder 26)
- Greater Fall River Joint Board, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 27)
- Greater Fall River Joint Board (Textile), 1982 (Box 62, Folder 28)
- Greater New York Joint Board, 1977-1987 (Box 62, Folder 29)
- Greater North Eastern Joint Board, 1984-1986 (Box 62, Folder 30)
- Greater Northern Textile Joint Board, 1984-1987 (Box 62, Folder 31)
- Greater Toronto Joint Board, 1986-1987 (Box 62, Folder 32)
- Headwear and Allied Workers Joint Board, 1985-1987 (Box 62, Folder 33)
- Hudson Valley Joint Board, 1985-1987 (Box 62, Folder 34)
- Indiana Kentucky Joint Board, 1986-1987 (Box 62, Folder 35)
- Kansas City Joint Board, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 36)
- Lehigh Valley Joint Board, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 37)
- Maine Joint Board, 1982-1987 (Box 62, Folder 38)
- Memphis Area Joint Board, 1982-1984 (Box 62, Folder 39)
- Mid Atlantic Regional Joint Board, 1984-1987 (Box 62, Folder 40)
- Mid South Region Joint Board Mid South Region Joint Board, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 41)
- Midwest Region Joint Board, 1984-1987 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Minnesota Joint Board, 1984-1987 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Montreal Joint Board, 1986-1987 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Neckwear Workers Joint Board, 1984-1987 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- New England Joint Board, 1982-1987 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- New York Joint Board, 1980-1987 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- NYS Regional Office (Textile), 1986 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Northern Jersey Joint Board, 1982-1987 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Northern California Joint Board, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  Note "(Closed-1983)"
- Pacific Northwest Joint Board, 1982-1987 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board, 1985-1987 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania Keystone Joint Board, 1978-1984 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Philadelphia (Textile), 1985-1987 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1985-1987 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Pittsburgh Joint Board, 1985-1987 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board, 1981-1986 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Quebec Joint Board, 1986-1987 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Quin-State Region Joint Board, 1980-1983 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Rhode Island State Joint Board, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 19)
- Roanoke Valley Joint Board, 1986-1987 (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Rochester Joint Board, 1985-1987 (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Rocky Mountain District Joint Board, 1985-1986 (Box 63, Folder 22)
- Saint Louis Joint Board (Textile), 1984-1986 (Box 63, Folder 23)
- Saint Paul Minnesota Joint Board, 1985-1986 (Box 63, Folder 24)
- San Antonio Joint Board, 1985-1987 (Box 63, Folder 25)
- Scranton Wilkes-Barre Joint Board, 1982-1985 (Box 63, Folder 26)
- Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Joint Board, 1985-1987 (Box 63, Folder 27)
- Shoe Service Union: Local 563, 1985-1987 (Box 63, Folder 28)
- South Carolina Coastal Joint Board, 1983-1987 (Box 63, Folder 29)
- Southeastern Regional Joint Board, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 30)
- Southern New England Joint Board, 1984-1987 (Box 63, Folder 31)
- Southern Regional Joint Board (Clothing), 1987 (Box 63, Folder 32)
- Southern Textile Regional Joint Board, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 33)
- Union Privilege, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- United Housing Foundation: Community Services Incorporated, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- United Nations Association of the United States of America, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- United Automobile Workers, 1985-1987 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- United Food and Commercial Workers International Union, 1980-1987 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- United Garment Workers, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- United Paperworkers International Union, 1984-1987 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1985-1987 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- United Textile Workers of America, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Twin City Joint Board, 1982-1987 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- West Coast Regional Joint Board, 1974-1985 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Western Carolinas Joint Board, 1983-1987 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Western New York Joint Board, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Western Ontario Joint Board, 1985-1987 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Unions Other Than Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- American Postal Workers Union, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Canadian Paper Worker Union (CLC), 1987 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Communications Workers of America, 1984-1987 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- International Association of Machinists, 1983-1986 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- International Federation of Chemical, Energy and General Workers Union, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 21)
- International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried Machine and Furniture Workers, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 22)
- International Association of Letter Carriers, 1985-1987 (Box 64, Folder 23)
- Service Employees International Union, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 24)
- South Jersey Joint Board, 1984-1987 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1983-1987 (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Southwestern Ontario Joint Board, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 27)
- Texas Joint Board, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 28)
- Tidewater Joint Board, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 29)
- Toronto Joint Board, 1977-1987 (Box 64, Folder 30)
- Unions Other Than Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 31)
- P Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- R Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- D Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- S Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- U Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- V Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- W Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Y Miscellaneous, 1983-1987 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- United Nations Association of the United States of America: Board of Governors Meetings, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- A Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- B Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- C Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- D Miscellaneous, 1983-1987 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- E Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- F Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- G Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- H Miscellaneous, 1984-1987 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- I Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 18)
- J Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- K Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 20)
- L Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- M Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 22)
- N Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 23)
- Social Services Chicago, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Social Services: Staff, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Social Services G.O. Reports, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Social Services Department: Students, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Social Services: Request for our Material, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Social Services: JP Stevens, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Social Service Training, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Social Services: Request for our Material, 1975-1976 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Social Services: Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Social Services American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Social Services Bi-County, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Social Services California, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Unnamed Folder, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Social Services Southwest Regional, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Social Services, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Social Services Pennsylvania, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Social Services Pittsburgh, 1978-1979 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- Social Services San Antonio, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 18)
- Social Services Saint Louis, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 19)
- Social Services Northeast, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 20)
- Social Services: Office Staff Meetings, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 21)
- Social Services New Orleans, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- Social Services New York City, 1975-1979 (Box 66, Folder 23)
- Social Services New York State, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 24)
- Social Services New England, 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder 25)
- Social Services El Paso, 1975-1976 (Box 66, Folder 26)
- Social Services Federal, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 27)
- Social Services General, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 28)
- Social Services Interns, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 29)
- Social Services Chicago, 1975-1978 (Box 66, Folder 30)
- Social Services Cincinnati, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 31)
- Social Services Cleveland, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 32)
- Social Services Colorado and Utah, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 33)
- Social Services Ohio, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 34)
- Social Services Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 35)
- Social Services Legislation, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 36)
- Social Services Marcus Hook, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 37)
- Social Services Local 169, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 38)
- Social Services Maine, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 39)
- Social Services Midwest, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 40)
- Social Services New Jersey, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 41)
- Social Services National, 1974-1977 (Box 66, Folder 42)
- Project Advisory Board, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Project Advisory Board, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  January 30, 1979
- Project Administrative Manual, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Placement International Business Machines, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Placement Just One Break, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Placement Mainstream, 1975-1979 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Placement Others, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Project Abstract (Box 67, Folder 8)
  No Date
- Project Administration of Grant, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Placement Help through Industry Retraining and Employment (HIRE), 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Rehabilitation New York State Advisory Council, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Periodicals, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Project Advisory Board, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Project job Analysis and Accommodations (Box 67, Folder 15)
- Project Consultant Services, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 16)
- Project Dissemination, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 17)
- Project Employment Forms, 1975-1976 (Box 67, Folder 18)
- Project Evaluation, 1978-1979 (Box 67, Folder 19)
- Retirees New England, 1974-1977 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Retirees New Jersey, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Retirees New Orleans, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Retiree Program General Office (Box 68, Folder 4)
- New York, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Retirees New York Joint Board, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Retirees New York Coalition, 1975-1976 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Retirees: New York University, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Retirees from North Carolina, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Retirees: New England, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Retirees: Omaha, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Retirees: Chicago, 1973-1979 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Retirees Chicago Joint Board Local 199, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Retirees: Cleveland, 1974-1979 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Retirees: Connecticut, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Retiree: Florida, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Retirees: Kentucky (Box 68, Folder 17)
- Retirees: Kentuckiana, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- Retirees: Los Angeles, 1975-1977 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- Retirees: Minnesota, 1973-1977 (Box 68, Folder 20)
- Unnamed Folder, 1975-1978 (Box 68, Folder 21)
- Retirees: Canada, 1973-1977 (Box 68, Folder 22)
- Retirees: California North, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 23)
- Retirees: Central States, 1974-1977 (Box 68, Folder 24)
- Retiree Program: New York City, 1975-1979 (Box 68, Folder 25)
- Retirees: Options, 1974-1977 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Retirees: Pennsylvania, 1977-1979 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Retirees: Philadelphia, 1974-1977 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Retired Members Questionnaire (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Retirees: Rochester, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Retirees: San Diego California, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Retirees: Saint Louis, 1974-1978 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Retirees: Shirt and Leisurewear, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Retirees: Southern California, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Retirees: Synthetics Joint Board, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Retirees: Textile Division, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Retirees: Washington District of Columbia, 1973-1974 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Retirement Early, 1962-1974 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Retirement: Pre, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Retiree Work, 1972-1976 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- Social Benefits ACWA, 1973-1977 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Social Services Booklet, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 17)
- Social Service Department Budget, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 18)
- Social Services Field Staff Meeting, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  October 6, 1977
- Social Services Meeting, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  June 20-21, 1977
- Social Services ACWA, 1974-1976 (Box 69, Folder 21)
- Social Services Staff Meeting, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  May 21, 1975
- Rehabilitation Association for Children With Retarded Mental Development, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Questionnaires, 1973-1979 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Questionnaires, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Disabilities, 1979-1980 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Project Survey Design (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Legislation New York, 1975-1977 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Project Training Program, 1975-1978 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Project Progress Report, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Project Resumes, 1976-1979 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Legislation: State Addresses (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Legislation: State Arkansas, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  July 1978
- Legislation: State California, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Legislation: State Illinois, 1975-1977 (Box 70, Folder 13)
- Legislation: State Michigan, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 14)
- Legislation: State Minnesota, 1976 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  July 1976
- Legislation: State New Jersey (Box 70, Folder 16)
- Legislation: State North Carolina, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 17)
- Legislation Pennsylvania, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Legislation - State Texas, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Meeting: Enteen Minutes of Meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 70, Folder 20)
- Rehabilitation Burke Rehab Center, 1977-1979 (Box 70, Folder 21)
- Rehabilitation Chips, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 22)
- Rehabilitation Easter Seal Goodwill Industries, 1973-1977 (Box 70, Folder 23)
- Rehabilitation Federation Employment and Guidance Service, 1974-1976 (Box 70, Folder 24)
- Request for Information, 1977-1979 (Box 70, Folder 25)
- Project Staff Meetings, 1976-1978 (Box 70, Folder 26)
- Rehabilitation Accent on Living, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 27)
- Rehabilitation Altro Workshops, 1963-1977 (Box 70, Folder 28)
- Rehabilitation Association of Rehab Facilities, 1978-1979 (Box 70, Folder 29)
- Rehabilitation Federation of the Handicapped, 1966-1978 (Box 70, Folder 30)
- Rehabilitation Foundation for the Blind, 1977-1979 (Box 70, Folder 31)
- Disabilities, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Rehabilitation Harold Russell Associates Burke Rehab, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Rehabilitation Human Resource Center, 1975-1979 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Rehabilitation NJ Affirmative Action Advisory Board, 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Rehabilitation New Jersey Commission for the Blind, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Rehabilitation Institute of Applied Human Dynamics, 1975-1976 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Rehabilitation Jewish Guild for the Blind, 1969-1978 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Rehabilitation National Federation of the Blind, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Rehabilitation National Paraplegia Foundation, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Rehabilitation National Technical Institute for the Deaf, 1978-1980 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Rehabilitation New Brunswick Rehab Center, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Legislation: Federal Architecture, 1976-1979 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Legislation: Federal Dole-Mondale Act, 1976-1978 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Legislation: Federal Office of Federal Contract Compliance, 1976-1979 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Legislation Federal Other, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Legislation: Federal Pending, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Legislation: Federal Section 501, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Legislation: Federal Section 502, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Rehabilitation New York State Council on the Handicapped (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Rehabilitation President's Committee, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Legislation Federal: Sheltered Workshops, 1976-1978 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Legislation Federal Transportation, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Legislation Federal Section 504, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Education, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Federal Government Employment of Handicapped, 1975-1976 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- Federal Government: Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder 15)
- Federal Government: Office of Handicapped Individuals, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 16)
- Forms: Case Handling and Letters, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 17)
- Insurance, 1975-1977 (Box 72, Folder 18)
- Journals, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Journals Affirmative Action Report, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- Correspondence Elaine Finley, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 21)
- Correspondence Harry Gordon, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 22)
- Correspondence Althea Johnson, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 23)
- Consortium Washington District of Columbia, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  March 19-22, 1978
- Contracts, 1972-1977 (Box 72, Folder 25)
- Consortium State of Washington, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 26)
- Consortium New Haven, 1978-1979 (Box 72, Folder 27)
- Consortium New Haven, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 28)
- Consortium New Haven, 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Consortium Columbia School of Social Work, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Consortium Columbia School of Social Work, 1976-1978 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Architecture Barriers, 1976-1979 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Architecture Conferences, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Architecture Standards, 1961-1974 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Brochures, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Consortium Columbia School of Social Work, 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Workers Compensation North Carolina, 1978-1980 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Correspondence Joyce Miller, 1977-1979 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Interviews Business Representatives, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Interviews Chairpersons (Box 74, Folder 3)
  No date
- A "How-To" Guide for Labor's Involvement With Disabled Individuals (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Interviews Disabled Workers, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Interviews Shop Stewards, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Case Reports, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Correspondence Mike McArdle, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- White House Conference, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- White House Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Speeches General, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Speeches General, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Petti Cash, 1986-1989 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- New York City 182's, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Gloversville, 1980-1982 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Syracuse, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  Contains "Syracuse 180" "Syracuse 181" and "Syracuse 182" folders
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Outreach Program Leather and Clothing Workers Questionnaire, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- New York City 180's, 1986-1987 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- New York City 181's, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Outreach Follow-Up Nettleton Shoe workers, 1986-1987 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Employer Company, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Peer Outreach Workers Form (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Certificates (Box 76, Folder 3)
  No date, English and Spanish
- Headwear Certification (Box 76, Folder 4)